https://www.alphatrust.com/company/privacy_policy

Privacy Policy
AlphaTrust is dedicated to your personal privacy and data protection. We offer full transparency into how and why we collect personal inform so our customers can interact with us confidentially.
Personal Data that is Collected
We may collect any information you provide when contacting us by email, phone or via our website. We may also collect payment data, such as credit card information, including your billing address. Please note, that your credit card transactions will be processed by a secure, third-party credit card payment processor.
Personal Data that is Published We never publish the personal information of our customers or visitors.
Website Visitors Visitors to our website may have information from their web browsers logged for security and statistical purposes, as well as to enhance the quality of their browsing experience.
Online Signature Service Users AlphaTrust offers an online service, PRONTOSign™ ONLINE, for the processing of our customer's forms and documents for electronic signature and archiving. We do not control the content of our customer's documents or the information they collect, including non-public personal data. Such information may be stored for our clients within AlphaTrust’s products.
Online Demonstrations Users AlphaTrust offers online demonstrations of our software and services.  If you participate in these demonstrations, any data you enter may be retained by our systems. You will not be required to enter any personal data. However, you will have the option to provide an email address if you would like a copy of the sample document you signed during the demonstration.
Cookies Cookies may be used to help manage transactions. We do not store cookies on your hard drive, but instead use session cookies during your browser session only.
Communications from AlphaTrust As a customer, you may receive periodic communications from our company. Rest assured that we will not provide your contact information to any third-parties for marketing purposes; with the exception of AlphaTrust’s current and future parent and subsidiary organizations.
Data Security AlphaTrust employees who help administer your products and services have restricted access to your personal data.
External Links The AlphaTrust website contains links to external websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are no longer protected by the rules that govern the AlphaTrust website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites, as they may differ from our own.
Privacy Policy Changes AlphaTrust reserves the right to update this policy at any time.
Changes to Personal Information
If you should have any changes or updates to your personal information, please notify us via email at support@alphatrust.com or send mail addressed to AlphaTrust Corporation at 8226 Douglas Ave., Suite 625, Dallas, TX 75225 USA.
Questions? Should you have any questions about AlphaTrust’s privacy policy or our website, please contact us at support@alphatrust.com.
CONTACT DETAILS
Phone:     +1.214.234.9200Toll Free:      866.613.7446Fax:          +1.214.292.8753Email:      info@alphatrust.com
Press Releases (17)
Follow AlphaTrust on:
